YYeTs.com
人人影視
*Better pray for hell*
時間軸： 濃子   萌    校對： 蘇小黛   胖兔純
What is it?
這到底是什么
Tell me.
告訴我
And why you felt the need to detroy it.
你為什么要銷毀它
Tell you?
告訴你什么
Was it not you who just told me
好像是你告訴我的
that it was a magical transporting mask?
這是個神奇的瞬移面具吧
Did I get that right?
我沒說錯吧
Don't you dare mock me.
別糊弄我
I've afforded you the privacy to explain.
我給了你很多次機會  讓你私下解釋
Which I have done many times.
你還要我說多少次
It is an artifact of my travels.
這是我旅行時買的工藝品
Stop.
夠了
No more lies. I simply want the truth.
別再騙我了  我只想知道真相
The truth of the mask?
這個面具的真相嗎
The truth of you.
你的真相
Of who and what you are.
你到底是什么身份
Fine.
好吧
Perhaps there is someone who is not yet tired of my questions,
也許有人不會嫌我問題多
someone with knowledge of other worlds
一個熟知外面的世界
who isn't afraid to share it.
并且不畏分享的人
Increase Mather.
英克里斯·麥哲
What on earth would you want to bother him
為什么你一定要拿這種荒唐的事兒
with this nonsense for?
去麻煩人家呢
Nonsense?
荒唐
Why don't we see if Increase regards this as nonsense?
那不如去讓英克里斯鑒定一下吧
For I do not believe he will.
我相信他不會覺得荒唐
Anne.
安
Do you know why I came back to Salem?
你知道我為什么要回到塞勒姆嗎
Lovely.
呵呵
More questions I can answer to your dissatisfaction.
我的回答只會讓你不滿
Not only to hunt witches,
我回來不只是為了追捕巫師
but to make a man of my son.
更重要的是讓我兒子成人
You found some witches?
你抓到幾個巫師
So your trip is not a total loss.
那你也算不虛此行了
Do you really not see the path that I've set you on?
你真的看不見我為你鋪好的路嗎
The whore is gone.
那個妓女已經不在了
A rare opportunity awaits you now
現在正是千載難逢的機會
to announce yourself before the entire province.
你可以在塞勒姆所有人民面前宣告自己
And what is that?
宣告什么
Tomorrow I shall bring John Alden's case before the board.
明天我會將約翰·奧登的案子提交委員會
Cotton, you are a persuasive... nay, a gifted speaker.
柯頓  你是個既有天賦又有說服力的發言人
I want you there by my side.
我希望你支持我
I will not.
我不去
John Alden is my friend, perhaps my only one.
約翰·奧登是我的朋友  可能是我唯一的朋友
And you would allow friendship
你會讓友情
to stand in the way of your own elevation?
阻擋你自我提升的步伐嗎
He is innocent.
他是無辜的
And you know it.
你明明知道
Do I?
我知道嗎
Do you?
你又知道嗎
A man shares your whiskey and suddenly you can...
他就是你的酒肉朋友  突然你就能
you can see into his very soul
就能看清他的靈魂
and attest that it has not been blackened by the devil.
證明他沒被惡魔侵蝕走向黑暗了嗎
I, myself, possess no such omniscience.
我可沒有這番本事
You know, long ago, I faced the same dilemma as you.
很久以前  我也面臨過同樣的困境
It was state the case against a fellow student, a classmate,
我要么跟一個我很喜歡的同學反目
a young man I... I quite liked
一個我喜歡的年輕人
or remain silent and allow an accused witch to walk free.
要么緘口不語  放走一個被指控的巫師
And let me guess.
讓我猜猜
You watched him burn.
你眼睜睜看著他被燒死了
No.
沒有
I let my feelings intercede, and the young man was freed.
我的情感打敗了理智  那個年輕人被釋放了
And two years later,
可是兩年后
he slit the throats of two virgins in a satanic ritual.
他在一次邪教儀式上把兩個處女割喉了
My mistake.
都怪我
And it has haunted me ever since.
此后我便一直心存愧疚
So consider carefully your decision.
所以考慮好你的決定
You know me well.
你很了解我
Just how well do you know John Alden?
但你有多了解約翰·奧登呢
I surveyed the board per your request.
按照你的要求  我調查了委員會成員
And?
結果呢
Six of the selectmen will, indeed,
六位委員確定
opt to take Alden to trial.
會選擇讓奧登受審
The other five, loyal to the memory of his father,
其余五位  念及昔日他的父親
will vote for dismissal.
會投反對票
That leaves two seats.
還有兩個席位
I shall vote as you have asked.
我會按照你的要求投票
I assure you.
我保證
So this leaves me,
那就只能由我
as a proxy for my ailing husband, to break the tie.
作為病重丈夫的代表  打破平衡僵局了
Come. Let's get this over with.
來  我們把這件事解決了
Must we not hold all our citizens,
所有人民
both commoner and the sons of privilege,
不論貧窮富貴
to the same standard?
標準面前無一例外
When they cheat, must they not be pilloried?
如若不忠  必將上頸手枷
When they steal, must they not be whipped?
如若偷竊  必將施以鞭刑
And when they fail to uphold their promise to God and choose,
如若背棄對上帝的承諾
instead, to take league with the devil,
選擇與惡魔為伍
must they not then be judged by their decision?
必將因此受到審判
Thank you, Reverend.
謝謝  牧師
I believe the board is ready to vote.
相信委員會已做好投票準備
Captain Alden has been accused of the practice of witchcraft.
奧登上尉被指控施以巫術
The good reverend has graciously agreed
牧師慷慨同意
to allow the board to decide whether he should go to trial.
讓委員會決定他是否要接受審判
So, those who believe
所以  認為奧登上尉
that captain Alden should be tried as a witch?
應該被當做巫師接受審判的人有誰
Six for trial.
六人同意審判
And those who believe
那認為奧登上尉
that captain Alden's distinguished character
為人正直  此項指控
renders such accusations baseless?
毫無根據的有誰
Five for dismissal.
五人反對審判
Mr. Hale?
霍爾先生
Salem awaits your vote.
塞勒姆人民在等待你的投票
Dismissal.
反對
Six to six.
六比六
Which means I must break the deadlock.
也就是說決定性的一票在我手上
And I shall cast my vote --
我投...
Actually, Mrs. Sibley...
其實  西布里夫人
Your vote is not required.
你不用投票
You will be pleased to learn
你肯定會很高興
that George's health has progressed,
因為喬治的身體狀況大有好轉
at least to the point where he is able to cast his own vote.
至少已經可以自己行使投票權了
Thank you, doctor.
謝謝你  醫生
Reverend, you yourself said that he was held in the witch's grip.
牧師  是你說他被巫師控制了
Perhaps. Perhaps not.
可能吧  也可能不是
His condition has steadily improved.
他的身體狀況已在穩步好轉
Improved? He cannot speak.
好轉  他都不能說話
He can barely move.
動也幾乎不能動
All he can do...is spit.
他就只會  吐痰
Yes, precisely.
正是
George, my dear old friend,
喬治  親愛的老朋友
if you can understand the words
如果你能理解
that I am speaking to you, please spit.
我現在說的話  請吐一口痰
This is ludicrous.
簡直荒唐
Actually, Mrs. Sibley, it is anything but.
西布里夫人  其實一點都不荒唐
Your husband is a selectman
你丈夫是委員
and he is eager to perform his civic duty.
他非常想履行自己的公民義務
Well, then. Sir?
那好  準備好了
And now, George, tell me -- do you believe that this man,
現在  喬治  你告訴我  你覺得
John Alden, should now stand trial?
約翰·奧登應不應該接受審判
Yea or nay?
同意還是反對
If your answer is in the affirmative,
如果你表示贊成
will you please spit?
請吐口水
Return him to the jail.
把他關回牢里
Captain Alden will stand trial
奧登上尉將接受審判
on the charge of witchcraft.
罪名為施用巫術
Open it.
開門
Yes, ma'am.
是  夫人
Now leave us.
退下
I warned you.
我警告過你
I told you that should you stay in Salem, you would die here.
我說過留在塞勒姆  你會死的
So you came here to remind me?
你是來提醒我的嗎
Or to bury me?
還是來送葬
I came to apologize.
我是來道歉的
Not for today's vote,
不是為了今天的投票
But for the one that I cast that sent you on this course.
而且為了我當初的選擇  害你淪落至此
Had I accepted your offer to go to New York,
要是我接受你的建議去紐約
far from this place,
遠離這里
we would know nothing of votes or trials or Increase Mather.
就不必理會英克里斯·麥哲的投票或是審判了
And if I hadn't gone to war
如果我不去打仗
or you hadn't married Sibley.
如果你不嫁給西布里
There was no one choice that sent our course awry.
我們今天的局面不是單一的選擇造成的
Listen to me.
聽我說
If you go to trial, they will hang you.
如果你接受審判  他們會絞死你
But there is still a way to prevent such a fate.
但還有辦法能逃過這一劫
They cannot try you if you are not here to be tried.
如果你離開  就無法接受審判了
Escape?
越獄嗎
- Is that what you...  - I will arrange it.
-你打算...  -我會安排好
It won't be easy, but properly planned.
這事不容易  但只要計劃周詳
I have resources, means at my disposal.
我有手段  人脈任我調遣
- Mary. - Far more widespread than you might imagine.
-瑪麗  -資源之廣遠超過你想象
Mary, no.
瑪麗  不要
I won't go.
我不走
But a trial will result with you in the gallows.
審判的結局只有上絞刑架
You must know this.
你得知道
You know, I always wondered why Giles Corey never fought back,
我一直不懂吉爾斯·科里為何不抵抗
why he let them press him to death
為何他寧可被逼至死
rather than plead to their charges.
也不肯認罪
But now I know.
現在我懂了
He knew he lost the moment he played their game,
他明白一旦遂了他們的心意就徹底輸了
dignified their madness.
就會令他們的瘋狂之舉顯得冠冕堂皇
So, no, I won't run, not from my birthplace.
所以我不會從我出生的地方逃走
I'd rather die here.
我寧愿死在這里
And so perhaps you will get your wish.
你或許能如愿以償
Reverend Mather?
麥哲牧師
You're the Hale girl.
你是霍爾家的小姐
Anne, sir.
安  先生
Do you wish to speak to me,
你是想跟我聊聊
or are you simply content to watch me eat?
還是只想觀看我用餐
I have a question...
我有個問題
of witches.
關于巫師
Indeed.
可不是嘛
Are you merely curious or have you encountered one?
你只是好奇  還是遇見巫師了
Well... Anne, there you are.
安  你在這兒啊
Interrupting Reverend Mather's dinner.
打擾麥哲牧師用餐了
She was querying me about witchcraft.
她在詢問有關巫術之事
Was she?
是嗎
Reverend Mather was about to answer my questions
麥哲牧師正準備回答我的問題
that others seem unable to answer truthfully.
而其他人都不能老實回答我
Well, perhaps I can be of some assistance
也許我能提供一些幫助
so the reverend can finish his meal in peace.
好讓牧師安心繼續用餐
Perhaps. But will you speak honestly?
也許  但你會老實回答嗎
I will.
我會的
Well, it is no matter to me.
我并不介意
Magistrate, Miss Hale.
治安官  霍爾小姐
No more lies.
別再說謊了
Have either of you tired of this game?
你們有誰玩累了嗎
For I assure you, I have not.
我向你們保證  我可不累
Mercy's too smart for you.
梅西比你聰明得多
We'll never tell you where she is.
我們絕不供出她的下落
Is that what you think?
你們是這么想的嗎
That we're here together
我們在這里
because I require your help in locating Mercy Lewis?
是因為我要你們幫忙找到梅西·路易絲嗎
No, no, no, no, no, no.
不不不
I am here as an act of charity.
我來這里是出于善舉
Charity?
善舉
Aid me in apprehending her and your lives will be spared.
幫我逮捕她  就能饒你們一命
But if you persist in defying me,
但要是你們負隅頑抗
I can offer you no alternative to the stake.
我無從選擇  唯有處死你們
Mercy won't let us die.
梅西不會讓我們死的
She will come for us.
她會來救我們
Perhaps such a thought comforts you in your sleepless night,
也許無眠長夜中這種想法能聊以慰藉
But I assure you,
但我向你們保證
I will find Mercy Lewis with or without your help.
不管你們是否幫忙  我都會找到梅西·路易絲
You're late.
你來晚了
Well, I'm sorry, my lady, but I have to take precautions
我很抱歉  但我也得小心提防
with Increase still searching for me.
英克里斯還在四處找我
You're right to.
你是對的
You offered a solution once for Increase,
關于英克里斯  你曾經提出了一個辦法
one that I dismissed,
被我否決了
but perhaps it was only my response which was misguided.
也許我當時的反應是錯誤的
So what are you saying?
你是什么意思
I'm saying that Increase Mather must die.
我是說英克里斯·麥哲必須死
And we are the ones to do it.
這件事得我們來做
Kill him?
殺了他嗎
But why now?
為什么是現在
The shadow he casts grows longer.
他的魔爪越伸越長
And Tituba's accusations jeopardize one that I care for deeply.
而緹圖芭的指控危及到了一個我很在乎的人
John Alden?
約翰·奧登
No.
不
My dear, dear Mercy.
我親愛的梅西
You.
是你
Your path from lost girl to devil's assistant
你從一個迷失少女成為惡魔的助手
is one that I walked, too.
這是我也走過的路
I would protect you as I would mine own self.
我會保護你  就像保護我自己一樣
Now, Tituba's released, rewarded for her treachery,
如今緹圖芭靠出賣我們換得釋放
And you live like an animal, hunted and fearful.
而你卻像個野獸般被追捕著  恐懼著
So how will I do it and when?
我要怎么做  何時動手
Easy, my dear.
別急  親愛的
Many a witch has sought to claim Increase's life
許多巫師曾試圖殺死英克里斯
And lost theirs in the process.
最后卻都丟了他們自己的小命
Our efforts must be planned...carefully.
我們的計劃必須考慮周全
Surely you must have a method in mind.
你一定已經想到辦法了吧
Yes.
沒錯
I do. Show me your fingers.
的確有  把手指給我看看
My fingers?
手指
These will do.
應該能行
For what?
什么能行
Now strike me.
襲擊我
My lady?
小姐
Tear at my flesh as you would your vilest enemy.
像對待敵人般撕扯我的血肉
Do not question your ears nor your faith.
不用懷疑你的耳朵和信仰
Do as I ask.
照我說的做
And soon you will understand.
你很快就會明白了
I was 8 years old when I watched my parents burn.
八歲時  我親眼看著父母被燒死
Timeless solution for exterminating witches.
火刑是消滅巫師亙古不變的方法
Do you know what it's like
你知道那是什么感覺嗎
To witness the death of those you love
眼睜睜看著
More than anyone else in the world?
你最愛的人死去
I can't imagine.
我無法想象
It teaches you what you are capable of.
那能讓你意識到自己的能力
The depths and limits you never knew you had.
那種深埋體內  你也許永遠不會察覺的能力
And, yet, even as their ashes lingered in the air,
然而  即便他們已被挫骨揚灰
Steps were taken to spare me a similar fate.
我卻幸免于難
So I was whisked from England, sent across the sea,
我被趕出英格蘭  漂洋過海
surviving plague and pestilence,
在瘟疫和鼠疫中幸存下來
to the new world.
來到了這個新世界
I was taken in by those loyal to the cause
我被忠誠的巫師信徒收養
who raised me with a twin mission...
他們養育我長大  并教會我兩件事
Teach me to harness the power of who I was
一是如何發掘出自身的能力
And yet to keep it hidden from the world.
同時隱藏這種能力不被世人所知
And then I was raising a family of my own
后來  我有了自己的家庭
knowing that those I held most precious
深知我最珍愛的兩個人
live in every bit the jeopardy that I do.
恰恰被我自己所危及著
Am I a witch?
我是巫師嗎
Yes.
是
But does that make me any less of a loving father?
但那會減少絲毫我對你的父愛嗎
No.
不會
Most certainly not.
絕對不會
Enter.
進來
I came as soon as you summoned me.
您一召喚我就來了
I suspect you're not pleased.
您好像不太高興
What happened, Mrs. Sibley?
怎么回事  西布里夫人
Oh, uh, this.
哦  這個啊
And here my own vanity convinced me
我還一直在自欺欺人
it was hardly noticeable.
以為不會有人注意到呢
Join me in tea,
陪我喝杯茶吧
and I will tell you my sad tale.
讓我跟你講講我的悲慘遭遇
I went to the woods,
我去了樹林
hoping to clear my mind after recent troubling events.
想整理一下思緒  最近的麻煩太多了
Sugar?
要糖嗎
No, thank you.
不用  謝謝
Lost in my own thoughts, I scarcely noticed her.
我沉浸在自己的世界里  沒注意到她
Drink, Isaac.
喝吧  艾薩克
Until she was upon me.
直到她撲到了我身上
Who?
誰
Mercy Lewis,
梅西·路易絲
who greeted me not with kindness
她沒有因為我曾經收留過她
for once taking her in...
而心懷感恩
But with violence and anger.
卻向我回報以暴力和憤怒
She finds me guilty for Tituba's accusations.
緹圖芭被指控  她認為我難逃其咎
as if I'm responsible for my servant's mind.
仿佛我還得對自己女仆的想法負責似的
Mrs. Sibley?
西布里夫人
Yes, Isaac?
怎么  艾薩克
The tea.
這茶
What about it?
怎么了
Is it making you warm or just sleepy?
讓你周身發熱了嗎  還是覺得很困
Both.
都有
Good. Then it's working.
很好  那說明有用了
I don't mind telling you this
我不介意告訴你實話
Because when you wake, you'll remember nothing.
因為等你醒了就什么都不記得了
Although I do regret using you like this.
不過我確實抱歉要這樣利用你
Even in Salem, there are those who deserve better.
即便在塞勒姆  也還有像你這樣的好人
But Increase knows that you're far too scared and guileless
但英克里斯深知你膽小本分
to betray him again.
不可能再次騙他
He will take your words as fact.
他會相信你的話
Words?
我的話
That hearing that Mercy lurked nearby,
你聽說梅西在附近出沒
you sought her in the woods.
于是去樹林里找她
But she was too quick, and she evaded you.
但她動作太快  被她逃脫了
Increase will parse your words
英克里斯會仔細分析你每一句話
until he is convinced they are truth.
直到他相信你說的是實話
So repeat after me, Isaac.
跟我重復一遍  艾薩克
"I went to the woods..."
"我去叢林里"
"...to find Mercy Lewis."
"為了找梅西·路易絲"
"Past the lake, beside the weeping tree, I spied her."
"穿過小河  在低垂的樹枝旁  我發現了她"
Very good. Again.
很好  再說一遍
Can we ever truly know our neighbor,
我們真的了解自己身邊的人嗎
trust that they are whom they seem to be,
相信他們就是看上去的那樣
who they would have us believe them to be?
那些他們想讓我們相信的形象
We are told that a young woman, a girl,
有人說某個年輕女子  小姑娘
really was a tool of the witches only to find that she is,
被當做巫師的工具  不料卻發現她
in fact, a witch herself.
實際上就是巫師本人
And now Salem's first son stands likewise accused.
如今  塞勒姆先驅者之子也被控以同樣罪名
Look around.
看看周圍
Look to either side.
看看你的左右
Look to your neighbor.
看看你身旁的人
And ask yourself,
捫心自問
"Friend or sorcerer?
他們是朋友還是男巫
Wife or witch?"
是妻子還是女巫
God or devil!
是上帝還是魔鬼
Who said that? Show yourself.
誰說的  出來
It is my son.
是我兒子啊
Pay him no mind.
不用理睬他
Do not reward him with your indulgence.
別用你們的寬容放縱他
You question who the people of Salem are
你以上帝之名問著
in the name of god.
塞勒姆的民眾都是誰
Yes?
然后呢
But should the people of Salem not question who you are?
但是塞勒姆的民眾該不該也問問你是誰
For how else would the devil appear...
因為魔鬼也會反其道而行
but in the cloak of the lord?
以上帝之名出現
Get out.
出去
You are drunk!
你喝醉了
Your rantings only serve to embarrass yourself.
你的大喊大叫只會給自己蒙羞
Remove yourself now.
現在出去
You will not?
還不走
I will remove you myself!
我親自送你走
Point the finger at her own father?
指認自己的父親
She would never.
她絕不會的
Are you certain of that?
你肯定嗎
Wasn't it just last night that I found her with Increase?
昨晚我才發現她和英克里斯在一起呢
She had no intention.
她沒有這個企圖
She was simply acting out.
就是裝裝樣子
Salem is filled with those who act out --
塞勒姆有一堆裝腔作勢的人
friends who act like enemies,
朋友裝成敵人
enemies who act as executioners.
敵人裝成判決者
This is all new to her.
這些對她來說都太陌生
Trust that, in time, she will accept it.
放心吧  她會慢慢接受的
Yes, and if not, what then?
是啊  但要是沒接受  又怎么辦
Then it may be time to tell her the rest of the story.
那就是時候告訴她剩下的故事了
I'm afraid that time has already come.
恐怕現在已經是時候了
Your story is really quite fantastic.
你的故事很是引人入勝
Mary Sibley attacked by Mercy Lewis.
瑪麗·西布里被梅西·路易絲攻擊了
Yes, sir.
是的  先生
And out of loyalty to Mary,
出于對瑪麗的忠誠
you followed the girl into the woods.
你追蹤那個姑娘進了叢林
Loyalty to Mary?
對瑪麗的忠誠
No, sir. Loyalty to you.
不是的  先生  是對您的忠誠
Me?
對我
Are you not eager to find the girl?
您不是急著想找那個姑娘嗎
Did you not tell me
您不是告訴我
to keep my eyes and ears open on your behalf?
要替您眼觀四路耳聽八方嗎
So when I learned she lurked at the wood's edge,
所以當我得知她出沒在叢林邊緣時
I sought her out, as I knew you would have wanted.
我就遵照您的意圖去尋找她了
This is called a cilice.
這叫刺撓
I wear this to remind myself of my own failing.
我穿著它來時刻提醒自己所犯下的罪惡
Does it surprise you, Isaac,
你是否很驚訝  艾薩克
to learn that even I have sins I must atone for?
當你聽到即使是我也身負罪惡
Have you ever sinned?
你犯過罪嗎
Not intentionally, sir.
有也不是故意的  先生
Are you sinning now?
你現在在犯罪嗎
Are you lying to me?
你是否在騙我
I speak the truth, reverend.
我說的是實話  牧師
I saw her, but could not catch her.
我看見她了  但是沒法抓住她
And can you recall where it was you last laid eyes on Mercy?
你還記得最后一次看見梅西是在哪兒嗎
Past the lake, beside the weeping tree, I spied her.
穿過小河  在低垂的樹枝旁  我發現了她
And you could -- you could lead me there?
你能帶我去那兒嗎
Yes, of course, sir.
是的  當然了  先生
Well, then.
那么
prepare yourself, my boy.
收拾一下吧  小伙子
For you and I...
我們兩個
are going witch hunting.
要去獵捕巫師了
Miss Hale.
霍爾小姐
Am I intruding, reverend?
是不是打擾到你了  牧師
Well, I was just about to enjoy my late-afternoon drink.
我正準備享用我的下午"茶"
Not to be confused, of course, with my early-evening drink,
可別把這跟我的晚"茶"弄混了
which I anticipate taking place shortly, as well.
不過也差不多是時候了
Perhaps?
你也來一杯嗎
Oh, no, thank you. I can not stay.
不用  謝謝  我不能久留
I simply came to say... I'm sorry.
我只是來說一聲  我很抱歉
For?
為了什么
Everything.
所有事
I have not treated you well...
我沒有好好對待你
nor entirely fairly.
也不完全公平
So my father has earned me your pity. Is that right?
所以說我父親的所為讓你覺得我很可憐  是嗎
No.
不
I simply see that we are alike.
我只是看到了我們的相似之處
Both children of complicated men.
都有一個心機深沉的父親
Magistrate Hale, complicated?
霍爾治安官  心機深沉嗎
In truth, he's always seemed a bit of a...
說實話  我總覺得他就是個
a simpleton to me.
單純的白癡
No, I assure you.
不  我向你保證
He is as complex as any man in Salem.
他和塞勒姆中的人一樣充滿心機
You have made quite a study of them -- witches.
聽說你對巫師頗有研究啊
For all my studies, I'm not sure I truly know a thing.
即便如此  我仍覺得自己對他們一無所知
Oh, I doubt that.
我可不這么認為
I'm sure you could tell me all about them.
你一定能告訴我許多關于他們的事情
I did not know you even believed in witches.
我還不知道你也相信巫師的存在
I've had a change of heart.
我改變了想法
And why is that?
為什么呢
Perhaps it is an interest I've lived with my entire life,
也許是我一直都對其有興趣
but wasn't aware of until recently.
但是直到最近才發現
Well, um...
好吧
If you have a moment, please sit,
如果你有時間  就請坐吧
and I will tell you all about witches.
我會告訴你關于巫師的一切
It's here, reverend.
就是這  牧師
You're sure?
你確定嗎
It was the trail I took that led me to her.
這就是那條通往她藏身之處的小路
Careful, sir.
小心點  先生
We do not know when she could strike.
我們得提防她的突然襲擊
Tell me, did you really travel
告訴我  你真的獨自一人
this deep into the woods alone
走進叢林深處
to find the girl?
只為了找到那個女孩嗎
For you, sir.
為了你  先生
For me?
為了我
I'm touched.
我很感動
I'm also extremely skeptical.
但我卻仍然無法相信你
Reverend?
牧師
What is your plan?
你到底有何意圖
Plan?
意圖
To lure me? To kill me?
引我來此  好對我下手嗎
No. Why would I? How?
不  我為什么要這么做
Or perhaps
或者說
perhaps you did not have a choice.
或者你別無選擇
Tell me, whose bidding is it that you do?
告訴我  你在為誰賣命
Is it John Alden who wants me dead?
是約翰·奧登想讓我死嗎
Or Mary Sibley?
還是瑪麗·西布里
Or do they work in concert?
又或者他倆同流合污
Tell me now or I'll slide this blade along your throat
馬上告訴我  不然我就順脖一刀
and you'll be dead before I clean and sheath it.
在我擦血入鞘之前你就會早已死透
Reverend, I promise you I'm here on your behalf
牧師  我發誓這么做都是為了您
and yours alone.
絕無二心
Sir!
先生
After her! Go on!
追上她  快去
You've seen one?
你曾親眼見過她們
A witch, I mean?
我是說  一個女巫
I have.
是的
A vile creature who walked undetected for years
這惡毒的老怪物多年來一直未被人識破
until finally her true nature was revealed.
幸好最終  她終究暴露了本性
So they hide amongst us?
就是說她們藏在我們之中嗎
This change of heart is remarkable.
這想法改變的真徹底
Remarkable that it took so long.
真不懂為什么我花了這么久才明白
Living in Salem and not believing in witches
生活在塞勒姆卻不相信有巫師
is like living in london and not believing in fog.
就如同生活在倫敦卻不相信有大霧一般
It is to deny what is right in front of you.
我居然傻到去否認擺在眼前的事實
And what does your father think of your conversion?
你父親怎么看待你這種轉變
My father...
我父親
above all is...
他正是
responsible for it.
轉變我看法的原因
Perhaps he's as complicated as you say.
或許他真如你說的一樣心機深沉
But what my father did not answer is...
但是我父親沒有說明的是
what do witches want?
巫師們想要什么
Some say they want only to live in peace.
有人說他們只想與我們和平共處
Others, like my father,
其他人  譬如我父親
say that they desire nothing less
說他們的目的只有一個
than the destruction of all mankind.
那就是將人類徹底滅絕
And is your father correct?
如果你父親是正確的呢
My father's correct in most matters.
我父親大多數時候都是正確的
Is he correct about you?
他對你的看法也是正確的嗎
My father thinks I'm a failure.
我父親認為我是個廢物
Since I have failed at both piety and sobriety.
因為我既不虔誠  還終日酗酒
Yes.
沒錯
The evidence supports his case.
我想這兩點大家都有目共睹
He's wrong.
他錯了
Another failure to add to my list.
如今我的失敗又加上了一件
Your only failure is not becoming your father.
你唯一的失敗就是沒有成為你的父親
And that is no failure.
而那根本不算失敗
Terra sunt carnes et ossa.
[咒語]
I do not see her.
我沒看到她
Fear not. She will return.
不用擔心  她會回來的
For how else can she attempt to kill me?
要不她還怎么殺掉我呢
Domini est terra et ossa.
[咒語]
Satan is a formidable enemy
撒旦是個強大的敵人
not because he's evil, but because he is sly.
不是因為他的邪惡  而是因為他很狡猾
Oh, we know each other well.
我們倆是老相識了
Et nos unum benedictus.
[咒語]
Reverend?
牧師
Sir?
先生
Sir? Reverend Mather?
先生  麥哲牧師
Looking for me, reverend?
在找我嗎  牧師
You will return with me to Salem,
我會將你抓回塞勒姆
and you will stand trial, witch.
你會受到審判的  巫師
I don't think so.
我可不這么認為
Did you think it would only take
難道你真的以為
one knife to kill me, reverend?
僅憑一把小刀便能殺了我嗎  牧師
After her!
快追上去
Isaac, don't let her get away!
艾薩克  別讓她跑了
Isaac!
艾薩克
Mercy's weapon.
梅西的武器
Oh, my poor boy.
可憐的孩子
Breathe shallow.
別用力呼吸
You are not alone.
有我陪著你
Yes?
什么事
Reverend Mather has requested you in his quarters.
麥哲牧師讓您去他那一趟
Cotton?
柯頓嗎
Uh, no, ma'am.
不  夫人
Increase.
是英克里斯
Mrs. Sibley,
西布里夫人
this way.
這邊請
May I have a moment with him?
能讓我單獨跟他待一陣嗎
Isaac.
艾薩克
Oh, sweet isaac.
親愛的艾薩克
I never intended for you to meet this fate.
我從未想過你會因此而受傷
So I promise you --
我向你保證
though a grim future awaits the people of Salem --
盡管塞勒姆即將迎來腥風血雨
I will protect you from any further pain.
但我不會讓你再受到任何傷害
I swear to you.
我向你保證
Come now.
我們出去吧
He needs his rest.
他需要休息
Reverend, I am at a loss.
牧師  我不明白
why Isaac would take it upon himself to seek out mercy...
為什么艾薩克會獨自一人去尋找梅西
I asked him the same question.
我也問了他同樣的問題
And what did he say?
他怎么說
He said he did it on my behalf,
他說是為了我
which I find very odd
但我卻無法相信
when you consider the fact that he detests me.
因為我很清楚  他十分憎恨我
Detests you?
憎恨您
No. No, isaac hates no one.
不  艾薩克不會恨任何人
He is incapable of it.
他做不到
Well, at least you will agree his mind is...
那至少你應該同意
childlike.
他就像個小孩
And, like a child,
正因如此
he absorbs the thoughts and the intents of others.
他會聽從別人的意識和想法
What others?
什么別人
Someone who does hate me...
那些真正恨我的
and desires me...dead.
想我死的人
And one other matter, reverend --
還有一件事  牧師
I remain skeptical that John Alden is a witch.
我對約翰·奧登是巫師一事仍心存懷疑
Ah, if not Alden,
如果不是奧登
tell me who, then, is responsible
那告訴我  到底是誰
for what has transpired in Salem?
導致了塞勒姆發生的一切
Regrettably, I do not know.
很可惜  我不知道
Well, perhaps we can hope together
或許我們可以一起祈禱
that the truly guilty party will step forward
那個真正有罪的人能站出來
and...exonerate the good captain.
洗脫上尉的罪名
Do you think that's a possibility, Mary?
你覺得這有可能嗎  瑪麗
This is Salem.
這里是塞勒姆
I think there are no limits to what is possible.
凡事皆有可能
Am I to expect another outburst?
你又是來沖我發脾氣的嗎
No.
不
I've not had a drink for hours.
我已經幾個小時沒沾酒了
Amazing what one comes to accept as a sign of progress.
真不敢相信你居然認為這也算進步
Why have you come at this hour?
你這個時候來做什么
I've been contemplating your offer.
我一直在考慮您的提議
To join you in the prosecution of captain Alden.
參與奧登上尉的審判
And you have seen the wisdom in it?
你終于想清楚我說的好處了
I have seen wisdom...
我確實明白了
But not yours.
但不是您說的那些
I've decided to defend captain Alden.
我決定為奧登上尉辯護
To defend?
為他辯護
Oh, imagine how proud I am to have...
你知道我有多驕傲嗎
raised a son so steadfast in his ability
看著我親手養育的兒子
to consistently make the wrong decision.
總是如此堅定地做出錯誤的決定
Anne.
安
Please, father, it's far past my bedtime.
明天再說吧  父親  我該睡了
I only require a moment.
我只要一小會
Something I neglected to tell you before...
有些事我一直沒有告訴你
regarding that mask.
是關于那個面具的
Truly, can this wait?
這事能晚點再說嗎
It has waited long enough.
不能再等了
And it is this
是這樣的
that the power of that mask
那個面具的能力
can only be accessed by those of one kind.
只能被一種人所激活
And what kind is that?
哪種人
My kind.
跟我一樣的人
But it worked when I...
但我激活了...
are you saying that I am...
你是說我是...
like me.
跟我一樣
A witch.
是個巫師